<?xml version="1.0"?>
<xml>
  <qna>
    <ques> What is the capital of India? </ques>
    <ans> New Delhi is capital of India </ans>
  </qna>
  
  <qna>
    <ques> What is the procedure to get rid of caffeine ?</ques>
    <ans> Nicotine patches are used to get rid of caffeine </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What is the procedure to make coffee ?</ques>
    <ans> Coffee is made using coffee beans </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What is the Currency of India? </ques>
    <ans> The Rupee (One Rupee=100 paise) is the national currency of India. </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What is the population of India?</ques>
    <ans> According to the 2011 Census, India's population is 1,21,01,93,422. </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What is the area of India? </ques>
    <ans> The area of India spans over 3.3 million square kilometers. </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What are the Official Languages of India? </ques>
    <ans> The official language of the Republic of India is Hindi with English as a secondary official language. </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What are the Major Religions of India? </ques>
    <ans> The Major Religions of India are Hinduism, Islam, Christianity, Buddhism, Sikhism and Jainism. </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What is the percentage of Literacy in India? </ques>
    <ans> India's literacy rate stands at 74.4 percent. </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What is the National Anthem of India? </ques>
    <ans> 'Jan gana mana' written by Rabindranath Tagore is the National Anthem of India. </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What is the National Song of India? </ques>
    <ans> Vande Mataram, composed in Sanskrit by Bankimchandra Chatterji is the National Song of India. </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What is the National Flag of India? </ques>
    <ans> The National Flag of India is a horizontal tricolor </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What is the National Animal of India?</ques>
    <ans> The Tiger (Panthera tigris) is the National Animal of India. </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What is the National Bird of India? </ques>
    <ans> The Peacock is the National Bird of India. </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What is the National Flower of India? </ques>
    <ans> The National Flower of India is the Lotus. </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What is the National Tree of India? </ques>
    <ans> The Banyan is the National Tree of India. </ans>
  </qna>

  <qna>
    <ques> What is the National Fruit of India? </ques>
    <ans> The Mango is the National Fruit of India. </ans>
  </qna>

</xml>
